<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
    <rss version="2.0">
      <channel>
        <title>Apjot</title>
        <link>https://apjot.blog</link>
        <description>A public journal of thoughts</description>
        <language>en</language>
        
      <item>
        <title>Navigating Gray Areas of conflict</title>
        <link>https://apjot.blog/blog/navigating-gray-areas-of-conflict</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 08:33:30 GMT</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[Delve into the intricacies of social interactions and cultural nuances as we explore the gray areas of racism, discrimination, and empathy. Join the discussion on understanding and navigating complex social issues - Exploring the Complexity of Social Issues Through Empathy and Awareness]]></description>
        </item>
      <item>
        <title>Memories (Spoken words)</title>
        <link>https://apjot.blog/blog/memories</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:52:43 GMT</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[null - the little moments ]]></description>
        </item>
      <item>
        <title>What’s in your Hand?</title>
        <link>https://apjot.blog/blog/whats-in-your-hand</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[Embark on a journey of spiritual rediscovery and self-realization, reflecting on the transformative power of God's guidance through ordinary circumstances. Explore the lessons from Exodus 3 and 4:2-5, discovering how to overcome doubtand insecurity - A journey of Faith: Embracing Divine Potential in the Ordinary]]></description>
        </item>
      <item>
        <title>Stoicism: Philosophy of Resilience.</title>
        <link>https://apjot.blog/blog/stoicism-resilience</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 08:31:35 GMT</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[null - Principles of Stocism ]]></description>
        </item>
      <item>
        <title>What If ?</title>
        <link>https://apjot.blog/blog/embracing-what-if-illuminating-perspectives</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 08:33:27 GMT</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[Explore thought-provoking "What If" scenarios and discover illuminating perspectives on life's journey. Embrace reflection, self-discovery, and authentic growth for a purposeful, fulfilled existence. - 10 Reflective Perspectives on Life
]]></description>
        </item>
      <item>
        <title>Understanding our Emotions</title>
        <link>https://apjot.blog/blog/understanding-our-emotions</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:22:45 GMT</pubDate>
        <description><![CDATA[ Dive into the world of emotions and uncover the hidden messages they hold. Develop emotional awareness, cultivate self-compassion, and embrace healthy coping mechanisms. Discover the power of emotional intelligence and the importance of support syst - Unveiling the Messages Within our Emotions
]]></description>
        </item>
      </channel>
    </rss>